Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 09.08.19 13:13:18
前情提要
Previously on Prison Break...
你和我是不一样的 Michael
There's one big difference between you and I, Michael.
你不会杀人
You can't kill.
我会抓到你的
I will get you.
这个给你 如果你在路上
This is, uh... in case you run into trouble
遇到麻烦
down the road.
Lincoln 他想见你和你弟弟
Lincoln, he really wants to see you and your brother.
Michael10岁以后他就没有见过了
He hasn't seen Michael since he was ten years old.
我们为什么要离开
Why are we going?
Michael从来没见过你爷爷
Michael never met your grandfather.
爸爸
Dad.
-我和Burrows家人在一起 -干掉他们
I got Burrows. Take care of them.
我想也许我很喜欢这样
I think there's a part of me that enjoys this.
我感觉是在
It feels to me like
追寻刺激
chasing a high.
并且我现在
And I should know better
全都懂了
by now.
Sara
Sara?
你好 Sara
Hi, Sara.
嘿 这是什么
Hey, what is this?
这是我用来量血压的
It's for my... blood pressure.
-Geary 求了你 我们做个交易 -没有交易
Geary, come on, we can make a deal, man. No deals.
你刚刚失去了还价的筹码
You just crapped out your last bargaining chip, pal.
这真是好东西
Ain't that the most beautiful thing you ever seen?
我们是Tribune警察局的
This is the Tribune Police.
请表明身份
Make yourself known.
嘿 你运气真好
Hey, you're in luck.
在后面找到一盒
Had a case in back.
太好了
Excellent.
渔具润滑油
Fishing reel oil.
一盒你全要吗
And you want the whole case?
一盒全要
Whole case.
你还要GPS
And the, uh, GPS?
还要GPS
And the GPS.
看来你是要钓大鱼
Must do quite a bit of fishing.
是的 要钓很多鱼
Yeah, a lot of fishing...
但不全是钓鱼的
not a whole lot of catching.
96.23美元
$96.23.
嗯
Um...
我还是只要渔具润滑油
I'm just going to take the reel oil.
谢谢
Thank you.
嘿 你还没付钱呢
Hey! You have to pay for that.
拿走就是了 别伤害我
Just take it; please don't hurt me.
求你了
Please.
你还没付钱呢
You have to pay for that.
保险柜 快打开
Vault. Open it.
为团体做贡献
One for the team.
他不是想对付我 而是对付我的女儿
He wasn't gunning for me, he was gunning for my daughter.
告诉Anna他父亲很爱她
Give Anna her papa's love.
我要割断你的脖子
I'm going cut your throat out.
我爱你 Michael
I loved you, Michael.
你利用了我
You just used me.
警察发现你的女朋友
Cops found your girlfriend
浑身苍白
fish-belly white,
呕吐不止
gargling her own puke.
你又不会在乎
And what do you care?
反正只要她
As long as she left
帮你把门打开
the door open.
能遇到你我很高兴
I feel very fortunate to have met you.
对不起 Henry
I'm sorry, Henry.
这关系于商业利益控制政府
It's about corporate interests taking over the government--
贿赂选举 挑起战争
buying elections, fighting wars...
无辜者丧命 他们可以获利
people dying so they can turn a profit.
我们想阻止他们
We're trying to stop it.
你们是什么 一群间谍吗
What are you, a bunch of spies?
一些参议员和众议员
Just a handful of senators, congressmen,
和我一样以前
people like me that once worked
为"公司"工作的人
for the company.
他们想揭发总统的
People willing to expose the President
真实身份
for what she is--
一个为那些集团服务的骗子
a shill working for these corporations.
我们搞垮她
We bring her down,
他们也就垮掉了
we bring them down.
这和我有什么关系
What's it got to do with me?
因为把她搞垮
Because the way we're going to bring her down
你也就自由了
is also what we're going to use to set you free.
一星期前 我们有了突破
About a week ago, we finally got a break.
一个内应的国家安全局分析员
An NSA analyst sympathetic to our cause
终于获得了安全许可
finally worked his way up and got clearance
可以接触到Echelon计划
into the Echelon program.
全国的电邮和电话
E-mails, cell phone calls all across this country,
只要发送出来 都会通过Echelon
if it's transmitted, it goes through Echelon.
然后被分类解析
It's catalogued, interpreted,
存储于国土安全部
and then stored for Homeland Security.
不放过蛛丝马迹
Nothing is missed by them.
都不放过
Nothing.
也包括
Including,
碰巧911后
by accident,
几个月内的
for a few months after 9-11...
白宫信息
the White House.
分析员无意中监听到了
The analyst got his hands on a phone conversation
总统和Terrence Steadman的电话
the President had with Terrence Steadman...
也就是你应该
two weeks after you
杀掉他的两星期后
supposedly killed him.
分析员本想把信息
Now, the analyst tried to get this information
带出大楼
out of the building...
结果有人盯上他了
...but it turns out, someone else was snooping, too.
有其他人想要
Someone else
质问总统
wanted answers about the President.
Aldo和Lincoln想单独呆一会
Aldo and Lincoln want to be left alone.
当然了 我明白
Sure, I understand.
24小时后 Tancredi就死掉了
24 hours later, Tancredi is dead,
分析员也不见了
the analyst is missing,
并且白宫的记录
and the White House Echelon tapes
也从主机中删除了
have been deleted from the mainframe.
磁带还在某处
The tape is still out there.
从他们费力追踪Sara Tancredi来看
And judging by how hard they're going after Sara Tancredi,
我想他们认为在她那儿
I'm pretty sure they think she has it.
并且他们是对的
And I think they're right.
她是整件事的关键
She's the key to this whole thing,
Lincoln
Lincoln.
-==http://www.1000fr.com==- 謦灵风软影视论坛荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
www.1000fr.com Present
Capture:FRM@FadeOut Sync:FRM@Navel
-=风软FRM字幕组=- 翻译:乐山刘凌 由仪 JJames 飞觞 校对:泰的 时间轴:Navel 酒囊饭袋
我想你觉得
I would imagine
你被出卖了
that you're feeling slightly betrayed right now.
这我明白
I understand.
如你所见
As you can see,
嗨 我不叫Lance 并且也不是酒鬼
hi, my name is not Lance, and I'm not an addict.
好吧
Okay.
我有个特点现在对你来说
There is one thing about me that should mean
显得十分得重要
a great deal to you right now.
那就是我很讲道理
That is I am reasonable.
如果你告诉我实情 我就放你走
If you tell me what you know, you get to go.
也许当这一切
Okay, and then maybe
结束之后
when this is all behind us,
我们可以叙叙旧
we get to grab a piece of pie for old times' sake.
好的
Okay.
我不知道Michael在哪儿
I don't know where Michael is.
这和Michael无关 是关于你父亲的
This is not about Michael; this is about your father.
他从华盛顿带走了些
He left Washington with something
不属于他的东西
that didn't belong to him.
我们想要回来
We need it back.
你就因此杀了他
And you killed him for it.
我没有 但是我认为
I didn't, no, for what that's worth.
他的死已经
But I hope that his death
说明了我们的麻烦
properly illustrates the magnitude
已经很严重了
of the situation that we're in right now.
东西在哪儿
So, where is it?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
东西在哪儿
Where is it?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
东西在哪儿
Where is it?
我不知道
I don't know what you're
你在说什么
talking about.
Sara 我还有下一步打算
Sara, there's a next step involved in this,
我想你不想承受的
and you don't want to experience that.
我发誓不知道你在说什么
I swear to God I don't know what you're talking about.
我父亲什么
My father didn't
都没有给我
give me anything.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
原谅我 神父 我犯罪了
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
你上次忏悔是什么时候
How long has it been since your last confession?
这是我第一次
This is my first time.
已经很久了
In a long time.
你知道你所犯错误的本质吗
Are you aware of the nature of your sins?
错误本质
The nature?
我不太清楚
I'm not really sure.
在你内心深处 你知道的
Deep down inside your heart, you know.
也许是正义吧
Righteousness, maybe.
为了目的可以不择手段
Believing the ends justify the means.
你的目的是什么
What are those ends?
拯救其他人的性命
Saving someone's life.
那么手段呢
And the means?
我触犯了所有的法律
I've broken just about every law you can name.
不仅是我的所作所为
But it's not just what I've done.
而是其他人犯下的错误
It's what others have done...
全是因为我
...because I let them.
因为我自以为做得正确
Because I was doing what I thought was right.
这次我应该更加清醒
I should have known better this time.
这一次
This time?
当我还是小孩时
When I was a kid...
我曾目睹一个人失血致死
I watched a man bleed out and die.
并且我很高兴
And I was glad...
因为他罪有应得
because he deserved it.
生命的本意就是
Life is
-上帝的给予和夺取 -突然间
only for God to give and take, my son. Suddenly,
我的心里就留下了阴影
there is this dark space inside of me.
并且我知道是错的
And I knew it was wrong.
但是我已经无法自拔
But here I am.
有个方法能让你解脱
Thereisa way to stop this.
在上帝面前改过自新
Surrender your will to God.
如果我现在放弃
If I surrender now,
我就失去我所爱的一切
I lose everything that I love.
但是在这过程中你却失去了灵魂
But do you lose your soul in the process?
听着 我们都要背负十字架的
Well, we all have our crosses to bear.
你还好吗
You okay?
这事会没完没了
This is never gonna stop.
他们会在我们后头紧追不舍
They're gonna keep coming after us.
Lincoln 别接
Lincoln, don't.
搞定没有
Is it done?
搞定了
You are.
Lincoln Burrows
Lincoln Burrows.
你的人死了
Your man's dead.
和其他你派来抓我儿子的人一样
Just like anyone else you send to take out my son.
我们只想抓你
We want you.
与LJ无关
This isn't about LJ.
有个非常简单的方法
There's a very simple way
让这一切结束
for all of this to end.
我来告诉你怎样了结…
I'll tell you how it's going to end--
那就是你会睁着你的死鱼眼睛 看着我的手勒在你的脖子上
me staring in your dead eye with my hand around your throat.
你都不知道我是谁
You don't even know who I am.
还有多远
How much further?
就在这儿停
Right here is good.
Thanks for the ride.
-谢谢你让我搭车 -不客气
Mahone探员
Agent Mahone.
Bill Kim
Bill Kim.
我来接你了
I'm here to pick you up.
我是给Kellerman打的电话
I called Kellerman.
他现在正忙
He's busy right now.
还有其他人知道你在这儿吗
Does anyone else know you're here?
-没有 -很好
No. Good.
你能打开这门吗
Can you open the gate?
而且我需要一辆新车
And I need a new vehicle.
关于我 有些事情你得了解
There's something you should know about me.
我不喜欢发飙的
I don't like being out in the field.
我只在事情办砸的时候才会那样
I only do so when there's been a screwup.
这会我已经发飙了 Alex
I'm out in the field, Alex.
那么你为什么不开门
Then why don't you open the gate?
你可以在你泥足深陷之前
You can hurry back to D.C.
赶紧回华府去
before your shoes get dirty.
我们有一条线索 是关于Burrows
We have a lead as to where Burrows
会在哪里和他的兄弟碰头
will be meeting up with his brother.
他提到那个地方叫"Bolshoi Booze"
It's a place he referred to as "Bolshoi Booze."
这让你想起什么来了吗
Does that mean anything to you?
是的 这是Scofield身上数以百计的纹身中的一个
Yeah, it's one of a hundred tattoos on Scofield's body.
那意味着什么
What does it mean?
我还不知道
I don't know yet.
在接下来的几个小时里
You'll need to figure it out
你得把它弄清楚
within the next couple of hours.
如果Scofield和Burrows越过了边界
If Scofield and Burrows cross the border,
他们就超出了你的管辖权范围
they'll be out of your jurisdiction,
那么对我们来说你也没有什么长远的价值了
and you'll be of no further value to us.
开门
Open the gate.
那么你能干点什么
So you can do what?
我倒想听一听
I want to hear it.
听听自认为是我们的终结者
Straight from the mouth of the guy
-亲口说出来 -我会抓住Scofield
who's supposed to be our closer. I'll get Scofield
还有Burrows… 和他们一伙的所有的人
and Burrows... and all of the rest of them.
那么我和你
And then me and you
还有Kellerman
and Kellerman,
我们分道扬镳
we're going to part ways.
我只是希望你能确定一个合适的目标
I just hope you're properly motivated.
因为只要你尽你的本分 我们就会忘掉Shales的事
'Cause as long as you do your job, we'll forget about Shales.
那样你就能回科罗拉多去看望你的儿子了
And then you can go back to Colorado and visit your son.
Cameron
Cameron.
他5岁了 对吗
He's five, right?
不许你再提他的名字
Don't you ever mention his name again.
就是这样
There he is.
这才是我想听到的
That's what I wanted to hear.
去干点什么吧 Alex
Get cracking, Alex.
许多人都在指望你
A lot of people are relying on you.
Jane会妥善处理一切 你可以信任她
Jane will take care of it; you can trust her.
我知道这很困难
I know this is hard,
但是会解决的 我向你保证
but it will work out-- you have my word.
-谢谢 -保重
Thank you. Be careful.
听着 呃…
Listen, uh...
我明白
I know.
Jane会照顾你的
Jane's gonna look after you.
我甚至都不认识她
I don't even know her.
她没问题
She's all right.
她为我爸爸工作一段时间了
She's been working for Dad for a while.
我会 呃…
I'll, uh...
我们很快就会见面 我保证
I'll see you soon, I promise.
以前你爸爸也跟你说过同样的话吧
Isn't that the same thing your dad told you?
是的 但是我是认真的
Yeah, but I mean it.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 是我
Hey, it's me.
你收到这留言就给我打电话 好吗
Just call me when you get this, okay?
这很重要
It's important.
这些数字…
the numbers...
这就是我要的货
Is that my payment?
医用硝化甘油
Medical nitroglycerine?
跟说好的一样
As promised.
Whoo.
你知道弄到这种等级的货有多难
You have no idea how hard it is to get this kind of grade.
即使是我接头人也一样
Even with my contacts.
到你结束这笔交易的时候了
It's time for your end of the deal.
那飞机在哪儿
Where's that plane gonna be?
他们会在降落前几小时打电话告诉我
They call me a couple of hours before with the drop-off point.
这样可以不让缉毒局盯上我们
It keeps the DEA off our backs.
所以这还得等上一段时间
Since it's going to be a while,
你大概想站在大太阳里等
you might want to stay out of the sun.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿
Hey.
有什么问题
Is there a problem?
他们是我的表兄
They're my cousins.
听着 你父亲
Now, after your father accessed
得到消息后
this information, he made
用他的手机
three calls
打了三通电话 都是给你的
from his cell phone, all to you.
他跟你说什么了
What did he tell you?
就说他要回芝加哥
Just that he was coming back to Chicago.
很好
Good.
你很诚实 很好
You're being honest. Good.
现在 从他飞机着陆到他回到家
Now, there's a half an hour between when your father landed
其间有半个小时去向不明
and when he got home that is unaccounted for.
我知道你去了他办公室
I know you stopped by his office.
-你在那里见到他了吗 -没有
Did you see him there? No.
我最后一次见到我父亲时 他已经死在了他的书房里
The last time I saw my father, he was dead in his study.
你父亲有没有让谁给过你什么东西
Did your father have anyone give you anything?
你以为因为我喜欢被你捆着
Do you think that I'm just withholding information
而故意隐瞒什么消息吗
because I like hanging out with you?
如果我知道什么
If I knew something,
我会告诉你 但我不知道
I would tell you; I don't.
对于这些事情我什么也不知道
I don't know anything about any of this.
真的
Really?
那么为什么你要把Linconln Burrows
Then why did you give your father the file
的文件给你父亲
on Lincoln Burrows?
你为什么要给Scofield留门
Why did you open the door for Scofield,
帮他逃跑 为什么Scofield
and help him escape? Why did Scofield
要给你寄这些密码纸条
send you those coded notes?
为什么你要到新墨西哥州来见他
Why did you come to New Mexico to meet him?
别想耍我 把我当成不懂事的孩子
Don't try to float a babe- in-the-woods routine by me.
那可真的会把我惹毛 所以…
It's really going to piss me off, so...
来吧
Come on.
Shh. Shh-shh.
你没事
You're okay.
Shh.
听着 Sara
Look, Sara.
我们还是来达成一个协议吧 你知道的 对吧
We're going to have to come to an understanding.
没错 你说得对 那是坐标
Yeah, you were right; they are coordinates.
把它们输入你的GPS
Plug them into your GPS.
他们会在新墨西哥州的 沙漠中定位一个地点
They'll take you to a spot in the New Mexico desert.
那地方四周基本都是空旷的
It's in the middle of nowhere, basically.
谢了
Thanks.
好的 没问题
Yeah, no problem.
长官 你要去见谁
Sir, who are you meeting?
见鬼 他在干什么
What the hell is he doing?
他要把我们排除在外 这就是他在做的
He's keeping us out of the loop, that's what he's doing.
通常亡命天涯的人都没什么健康可言
Constantly running from the law with a bad heart...
墨西哥 我们来的地方 那里有许多好东西
Mexico, where I'm from has got a lot of great things,
但是…医疗体系却不是其中之一
but... health care ain't one of them.
你还好吗
You all right?
你看起来有点儿紧张
You look a little nervous.
我并不是每天都干这事儿
I don't do this every day.
我只想得到那飞机的消息
I just want to get the information on that plane
然后 呃…
and, uh...
走人
move on.
就是这样
Is that it?
就这样
That's it.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你用不着担心…我们可不会
You don't have to worry-- we can't
让手握赏金的
go within 100 feet of a federal marshal
联邦警察离我们只有100英尺
to collect the reward,
因为我们可是美国和墨西哥通缉犯
'cause we got U.S. and Mexican warrants on our heads.
但是这架飞机是去巴拿马的…
But this plane to Panama...
坐下来
Sit down.
这一切都是为了你哥哥
This is all for your brother?
是的
Yes.
我有四个兄弟 两个在监狱里
I got four brothers, two in prison.
打电话问候 我会
Accept a call? Yes.
但是救他们出来
But break them out?
-简直是疯了 -我哥哥
Loco. My brother gave me
在我14岁生日的时候 送我一个棒球手套
a baseball mitt for my 14th birthday.
我欠他的
I owed him.
你比我好
You're a better man than I am.
现在还说不准
Time will tell.
他们不是该打电话来了吗… 关于那飞机
Shouldn't they have called by now... about the plane?
没错
Yeah.
要知道 我… 我有个问题
You know, I... I have a question.
我觉得
I thought
这些应该装在玻璃瓶子里
that these came in glass vials,
而不是塑料的
not plastic.
我也这么想 但是
I thought so, too, but the guy
把这些卖给我的那家伙说 他用塑料瓶装
I bought it from said he packed it in plastic
是为了长途运输中以防起火
for transportation over long distances to prevent a fire
或是爆炸
or an explosion.
真的吗
Really?
这我还真不知道
I never heard of that.
干什么
What's going on?
我们得验验质量如何
We're going to do a little quality control test.
这已经是最好的了
It's the best available.
我们有的是时间
We got time.
我只记得是一些黑人 20出头
For the last time, some black male, early 20s,
从我背后跳出来
jumped me from behind.
我没看清他长什么样
I didn't get a good look at his face.
袭击者从背后攻击你
The assailant attacked you from behind?
我刚才不是说了吗
That's what I just said.
他还能在你脑门儿上来一下子
Yet he managed to make contact square on your forehead.
正是
That's right.
用什么 回旋镖吗
With what? A boomerang?
算了吧 跟我说说到底怎么回事
Come on, why don't you tell me what happened?
我是个Illinois州退休的管教干部
Look, I'm a retired correctional officer out of Illinois.
看在同行份上睁一眼闭一眼吧 亲爱的
How about showing some professional courtesy, honey?
我是Roy Geary 请留言
This is Roy Geary. Leave a message.
你这个手脚不干净的王八蛋
You thieving son of a bitch.
你最好跪下
You better get down on your knees
求求老天爷别叫我找到你
and pray to God that I don't find you,
因为如果我找到你 给我听好了
because, if I do, mark my words,
我会把你大卸八块
I'm going to gut you bow to stern.
总统Reynolds 今早在Florida州的Tallahassee
President Reynolds was in Tallahassee, Florida,
出席Martin Kleinhenz
early this morning, attending a $5,000-a-plate
为再次竞选参议员
breakfast fund-raiser for Senator Martin Kleinhenz,
而举办的5千块一位的慈善捐赠早餐
who's running for reelection.
今天下午晚些时候 在她的记者招待会上
Later this afternoon, her press conference was derailed
当一位记者请她
when a reporter asked her to comment
对Lincoln Burrows的 再次出逃作出评论时
on Lincoln Burrows' escape from custody.
她拒绝回答
She declined.
在上任一个月后
It's become clear in her first month in office
她对这次追捕行动的紧密关注 已经在民众心中逐渐清晰了
that she cannot separate herself from this manhunt.
只要事情没有结果…
And as long as it continues...
…评论家说关于Burrows的话题仍将…
...pundits say that questions about Burrows will contin...
小姐们
Ladies.
开始狂欢吧
Let's get this party started.
30年来我一直恨你
The last 30 years, I've hated you.
你抛弃了我
You walked out on me.
你连Michael长什么样儿都不知道
You haven't even seen Michael.
我看到过他
I've seen him before.
不是在报纸上 爸爸
Not in the papers, Dad.
我一直不明白什么人会抛弃家人
Been trying to work out what kind of man abandons his family.
如今我也在做同样的事
Now I'm doing the same damn thing.
你会再见到他的
You'll see him again.
我会尽力的
I'll make sure of it.
还有多远
How much further?
大概三个小时车程
About three hours.
很快就好
It's gonna be a few minutes.
我哥哥很快就到
My brother should be here soon.
我应该站在外面 他好能看见我
Maybe I should go outside and make sure he can see me.
好主意
That's a good idea.
让Ernesto去就行了
I think I'm gonna send Ernesto to do it.
Ernesto 辛苦一下
Ernesto, por favor.
喂
Hello.
好的
Si.
好的 知道了
Bueno, te veo.
就等这个电话了吗
Was that the call?
是的
Yes, it was.
是飞机的事吗
About the plane?
怎么样
Como se llamas?
糖水
Agua con azucar.
Sugar water.
你犯了大错 兄弟
You just made a big mistake, blanquito.
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, okay?
我不是一个化学家
I'm not a chemist.
卖给我的那人说就是药用硝化甘油
The guy I bought it from swore it was medical nitro.
我们都被耍了
We both got screwed.
是的 但只有一个人要为此掏腰包
Yeah, but only one of us is gonna pay for it.
听着 我只想离开这儿
Look, I just want to get
你只想要钱
out of here, and you want your payment.
我哥哥马上就到
My brother's gonna be here soon.
我们会想办法
We'll work something out.
你只管开价吧
Just name your price.
我已经开过价了
I already named my price.
是你自己不守约
You didn't go through.
你哥哥什么时候到
When's your brother getting here?
你想一起把我们交公了 对吧
You were planning on turning us in the whole time, weren't you?
他什么时候和你会面
When's he supposed to meet you here?!
放下武器
Sueltalo.
放下枪 要么我就打死他
Drop it, or I'm gonna shoot him.
放了他 要么我就打死你
Let him go, or I'll shoot you.
-把枪放下 -我不会放下的
Suelta la pistola. Ey, no estoy judiendo.
放下枪
Sueltala, cabron!
闭嘴
在哪儿
Where is it?
我父亲什么都没给过我
My father didn't give me anything.
你把希望寄托在谁身上呢
Who you risking your life for?
Lincoln Burrows
Lincoln Burrows.
一个街头混混
Street thug.
这就是你关心的吗
And why is that your concern?
"希波克拉底誓言"里不是说 (古代西方医生开业誓言)
I mean, is there somewhere in the Hippocratic Oath
"我发誓把我的生命献给"
where it says, "I pledge to risk my life
"那些对我毫不关心的人"
for those who don't care about mine"?
"因为他们并不关心你"
'Cause they don't care about yours.
Burrows和Michael Scofield
Burrows and Michael Scofield
他们只是利用你
just used you.
世上还有和你一样执着的人
Are you that surprised that there are people in the world
你感到惊讶吗
who will stand up to people like you?
你没几天活头了
Are you that far gone?
说得不错
That's cute.
痛
Sad.
并快乐着
But cute.
Cleveland的什么地方
A Cleveland what?
别急 我慢慢跟你讲
Don't worry, I'll talk you through it.
我们这儿还有个
And we got
玻璃茶几
a glass coffee table right here.
绝对不行
Hell no.
1000块我就干
I'll do it for a thousand.
$500.
$1,000.
$750.
好吧
All right.
这是什么
What the hell?
出去
Leave.
知道吗
You know,
在军用品商店
it's amazing what you can pick up
总能找到好东西
at an Army-Navy store.
那些折磨你的点子 都是Bellick想出来的
All that torture stuff, that was Bellick's idea.
依我看 他做得有点过分了
And if you ask me, he took the whole thing way too far.
听着
Listen,
我跟你一半钱作为补偿如何
why don't I just give you half the money, and we call it a day?
好吧 四六开
All right, 60-40.
别这样 T 我们还可以再商量
Come on, T, we can deal.
飞机在哪儿降落
Where's the plane going to land?
去你的吧 胆小鬼
Kiss my ass, cobarde.
我们怎么办
What are we going to do?
我还没想好
I don't know yet.
从地面越境行不通
We're not going to get across the border on the ground.
没有飞机 我们就完了
Without that plane, we're screwed.
他失血过多
He's losing too much blood.
-他这样撑不了多久 -他要杀我们之前
He'll never make it like this. He should have thought
就应该知道后果
of that before he tried to kill us.
我们得送他去医院
We got to take him to a hospital,
要不他就死定了
or else he'll die.
拜托
Please.
告诉我们飞机在哪儿 就放你们走
The plane, and we'll let you go.
告诉我
Dicelo.
把一切都告诉我
Dicelo todo.
现在就告诉我
Dicelo ahora!
Finley路…
Finley Road...
从高速路8号出口出去 有一条飞机跑道
off of Highway 8, there's an airstrip.
就在那儿 成了吗 快放我们走
There, okay? Now let us go.
-我们走 -不 不 不
Let's go. No, no, no!
Michael 我们走
Michael, let's go.
行行好吧
Por favor... please.
Michael 我们走
Michael, let's go.
别这样 求你们别这样
Don't do this, please don't do this.
快走啊 Michael
Let's go, Michael.
如果是我们受伤了
If we were bleeding
他才不会高抬贵手
he would have not lifted a finger,
你知道的 他会把我们都杀了
you know that-- he was gonna kill us both.
-走吧 -不 并不是那么回事
Let's go. No, that's not true.
Michael 我们必须要赶到飞机那儿…
Michael, we're going to get to that plane...
别这样
Don't do this.
赶快走吧
Let's go now, please.
拜托 别这样好吗
Please don't do this, okay?!
-你闭嘴 -别这样
Callate! Don't do this.
别这样 可以吗
Don't do, all right?
别听他的
Don't listen to him!
求你了
Please.
Sara 我很担心你
Sara, I care about you.
这不是我的本意 Sara
This is not what I wanted, Sara.
我是Kellerman
Kellerman.
Sara怎么样啦
What's going on with Sara?
她有没有告诉你什么
Has she told you anything?
哪儿也不许去
Don't go anywhere.
现在不行
Not yet.
我一直都以为你很有说服力
I trust you've been... persuasive.
是的 没错
Yes, absolutely.
那就杀了她
Then kill her.
嗯 可她知道些什么
Well, she knows something.
你要是不听我的 连你都得玩完
You disobey me, you are done.
明白吗
Do you understand me?
杀了她灭口 Paul
Put her in the ground, Paul?
Michael
Michael.
我们走
Let's go.
-Michael -别动
Michael. Hold still.
Michael 这么干不行 我们赶快离开这儿
Michael, we're doing it wrong-- let's get out of here.
否则他会报警的
Now, he's gonna call the cops,
-或者召集他的手下… -他不会这么干的
or go get his buddies... He's not going to make it.
-你必须得… -闭嘴
You have to... Callate!
等我们安全了 再叫人放了他们也不迟
We'll call them when we get safe.
走吧 Michael 快走吧
Let's go-- Michael, let's go!
多谢
Thank you.
你们得立刻把他送到医院
You got to get him to a hospital right away.
好的
Okay.
等等
Wait. Wait.
嘿 伙计…
Hey, man...
不要去Finley路
Forget Finley Road.
飞机会在日落时分停在4号公路的
The plane is going to stop at the seven mile marker
7英里路标处
on Route 4 at sunset.
在那儿逗留5分钟
It's going to stop for five minutes.
然后就飞往
Then it's going to go
墨西哥的瓦哈卡
to Oaxaca, Mexico.
如果你们错过它就惨了
If you miss it, you're out of luck.
他在途中失血过多身亡
He bled out on the way over.
知道他的身份么
Any ID?
是的 Roy Geary 是个外地人
Yeah, Roy Geary, just an out-of-stater.
你认识他
You know him?
他是我的朋友
He's a friend of mine.
Bellick先生
Mr. Bellick?
怎么
Yeah.
你能不能回答几个问题
You mind answering a few more questions?
喂
Yeah.
我是Pam
It's Pam.
出什么事了
What's going on?
我只想跟你打个招呼
I just wanted to say hey.
嗯… 你还好吗
Well... are you all right?
你说过这很重要
You said it was important.
我知道事情变得有些讨厌了…
I know things got kind of ugly toward the...
你知道 越到后来越是这样
you know, the end.
嗯…我也变得讨厌了
Um... I got ugly.
但是我希望你能理解 出于一些客观原因
But I want you to know that, that there were circumstances
嗯…
that, uh...
你和Cameron
It was better that you and Cameron
还是不和我在一起比较好
that you were not with me.
你为什么要现在跟我说这些
Why are you telling me this now?
如果我还能重来一次…
If I had to do it all over again...
我不会选择这种方式
I'd do it different.
我会让一家人团圆
We'd still be a family.
我会为此不惜一切代价
I'd give anything for that.
我只是想让你知道
I just wanted you to know.
Alex…
Alex...
到底出什么事了
what's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
我打电话只是想说….
I just wanted to call to say that I was, uh....
我对不起你
...that I'm sorry
一切都是我不好
about everything.
你现在在哪儿
Where are you right now?
我可以去找你
I can come get you.
这真让人感动 是不是
Wouldn't that be nice, huh?
不 我是认真的 你在哪儿
No, I'm serious. Where are you?
还有一件事
One more thing.
如果你在媒体上看到什么消息…
If you hear anything in the media...
什么
What?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我爱你
帮我亲Cam一下好么
嗯… 我很高兴我把这个地方告诉了你
Well... I'm glad I told you about this place.
也很高兴我学会了怎么用GPS
I'm glad I figured out how to work a GPS.
你下次能不能把事情搞得再复杂点啊
Could you make it a little more difficult next time?
我欠你个情
I owe you one.
咱们扯平了
We're even.
不过该走了
But we got to leave.
Linc
Linc.
嘿 哥们儿
Hey, buddy.
你好吗
How are you doing?
-LJ在哪儿 -他很安全
Where's LJ? Safe.
-钱呢 -我一会儿再告诉你 我们得出发了
The money? I'll tell you later; we got to go.
我还带了个人来
I brought someone.
爸
Dad?
我们以前见过
We've met before.
我马上就得动手了 知道吗
This is happening right now, okay?
别逼我这么做
Don't make me do this.
就算我知道 也不会告诉你的
Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you.
你不会 是吗
You wouldn't? Really?
你怎么这么傻
Are you that stupid?
你怎么就这么傻呢
Are you that stupid?!
因为现在你马上就要死了
Because now you're going to die!
你就要死了 而你只要告诉我
You're going to die, and all you had to do
你父亲给了你什么东西
is tell me what your father gave you.
我知道我的选择是什么
I know my options.
如果不说 会被你杀了 而如果我说了
I can not tell you and die, or I can tell you
也一样会被你杀了
and still die.
不 你错了
No. Wrong.
Sara
Sara.
快 放聪明点
Come on, smarten up!
哪怕一辈子就这一次呢
For once in your life.
求你了
Please.
你去死
Go to hell.
哦 淹死是很恐怖的 别逼我干这种傻事
Huh? Drowning is horrific-- don't get me wrong--
但是一旦你放弃挣扎 让水灌到你肺里
but once you give in and let the water come into your lungs,
却会有一种
there's a certain
快感…我是这么听说的
euphoria... I hear.
我猜是痛并快乐着
I guess as a junkie,
但愿你会喜欢这种感觉
I thought maybe you'd appreciate that.
这是你自找的
You did this to yourself.
风软FRM字幕组作品 -==http://www.1000fr.com==- 欢迎加入
Welcome to www.1000fr.com